#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nguyen-chinh-phuong-diem-42735373 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Microsoft Excel
Microsoft Office
Administrative Assistants

# Nguyen Chinh Phuong Diem

HR Management - Total Rewards

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

# Summary

Experienced Human Resources Supervisor with a demonstrated history of working in the farming industry. Skilled in Microsoft Word, Communication, Team Building, Management, and Teamwork. Strong program and project management professional with a Certificate focused in HR career from BCC.

# Experience

### **KASIKORNBANK**

HR

March 2023 - Present (2 years 1 month)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

HR management in C&B function

Wall Street English
C&B SUPERVISOR
April 2017 - March 2023 (6 years)
Ho Chi Minh City

Apr 2017 to current: Wall Street English in District 3, Ho Chi Minh City C&B Supervisor

Responsible for all C&B functions, including:

- Payroll related activities:
- Make monthly time sheet reports for salary process
- Implement the monthly payroll for all staff working in accordance with Company policies
- Supervise the assistant in calculation payroll for temporary staff
- Make monthly payroll reports such as headcount report, OT report, . . .
- Social, Health and Unemployment Insurance:
- To register social, health and unemployment insurance contribution for new employees
- To do monthly social insurance reconciliation report
- To make monthly insurance related reports

- PIT:
- To apply for issuance PIT code for employees
- To register dependent relief
- To do monthly/ yearly PIT declaration and finalization
- Lead to maintain HR data, design report to optimize HR reporting system to meet internal and external teams' needs of HR data analysis, and also ensure HR data confidentiality.
- Maintain and develop current HR systems, to fully support HR team daily work and improve HR working efficiency
- Manage labor contracts for all staffs
- Follow up and update HR team any changes in labor regulations related to PIT, insurances, ... on time.

De Heus LLC HR & Admin Supervisor October 2010 - March 2017 (6 years 6 months) Hồ Chí Minh

2010-2017 De Heus LLC District 2, Ho Chi Minh City HR & Admin Supervisor

- Payroll calculation: salary, allowances, adjustments, overtime, unpaid leave, sick leave....) for all staffs based on the timesheet and overtime records.
- Monitoring the staff's Social Insurance and Health insurance, Unemployment insurance, Health care 24/24 in base company policy;
- Responsible to manage benefit and welfare function: Sickness, Marriage, Funeral....
- Update set up new comer checklist on HR software
- Manage Labor contract: new contract, renew contract
- Draft and control labor contract status and prepare contract to sign, Letter of salary adjustment,
- Employee recruitment for plant only.
- Follow up PIT code, deduction for dependent
- Monitoring and controlling all expenses related to administration and ensure the payment for customers, supporters, internal suppliers and office operation on time and correctly;

- Responsibility for visa, passports, residence cards, work permit ... for experts;
- To be manage and control car team: Fuel, maintenance, repairing ... as request of department, check cost oil payment monthly
- Supervisor security, cleaner, canteen teams.
- Management office;
- Responsibility for booking ticket, accommodation, arranging car for business in domestic or abroad under Company Policies;
- Controlling ISO system of HR
- Draft service contract, the decision, internal announcement n the company
- Carry out legal documents in need, manage corporate seal in company
- Manage the location of stationery on monthly, uniforms for worker as periodic
- Organize company events such as: Company trip -Teambuilding, Year End party, Birthday ...
- Other task assigned by HRM

### Education

Economic University in HCM

Bachelor's degree, Business Administration and Management,

General · (2008 - 2012)

### **BCC**

Certificate, HR career · (2014 - 2014)